Cos Cob Power Plant Records
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series III: Boiler office records, undated, 1915-1986
  - Reddy Heaters and Air Scoop Space Heaters: notes, printed material, safety instructions, owners manuals, ca. 1979 (Box 7:, Folder 111)
  - Rail Coal - North Apparatus: correspondence, blueprints, drawings, instructions, printed material, parts lists, notes, 1919-1956 (Box 7:, Folder 112)
  - Rail Coal - South Apparatus: notes, drawings, printed material, ca. 1940 (Box 7:, Folder 113)
  - Screen Hoist/Dock Pump: notes, printed material, instructions, drawings, various dates (Box 7:, Folder 114)
  - Oil, Filters, Pumps: Transformer Oil Equipment repair records, correspondence, notes, drawings, blueprints, publications, instructions, various dates (Box 7:, Folder 115)
  - Oil, Filters, Pumps: Turbine Oil Equipment publications, printed material, 1947-1950 (Box 7:, Folder 116)
  - Fire-Fighting Apparatus: packing lists, invoices, correspondence, memos, manuals, printed material, publications, drawings, 1948-1979 (Box 7:, Folder 117)
  - Monthly Fire Drill Reports: printed material, reports, correspondence, 1962-1969 (Box 7:, Folder 118)
  - Valve Motors: Boiler Room: instructions, printed material, instructions, parts lists, correspondence, notes, diagrams, drawings, blueprints, 1927-1952 (Box 7:, Folder 119)
  - Oil Circuit Breaker Prints: diagrams, blueprints, ca. 1945 (Box 7:, Folder 120)
  - Type CO Relays: inspection and repair records, 1947 + (Box 7:, Folder 121)
  - Signal Circuit Breakers: parts data, diagrams, 1946 (Box 7:, Folder 122)
  - Type B (Signal) Oil Circuit Breakers: blueprints, correspondence, 1949 (Box 7:, Folder 123)
  - DA 2O Automatic Circuit Breakers: blueprints, invoices, receipts, notes, 1945-1950 (Box 7:, Folder 124)
  - DK 15 & DK25 Automatic Circuit Breakers: specifications, instructions, blueprints, diagrams, 1927-1970 (Box 7:, Folder 125)
  - Westinghouse (manuals, parts catalogs): catalogs, instructions, 1916-1944 (Box 8:, Folder 126)
  - Mianus Dam Pumping Station: blueprints, notes, instructions, diagrams, 1949-1953 (Box 8:, Folder 127)
  - Relay Protection: correspondence, blueprints, diagrams, notes, reports, instructions, 1944-1950 (Box 8:, Folder 128)
  - CA6 Relays (Differential): instructions, diagrams, correspondence, 1939-1957 (Box 8:, Folder 129)
  - 60 ∼ (?) Frequency Meter: instructions, notes, correspondence, charts, 1943-1945 (Box 8:, Folder 130)
  - Switchboard Indicating Meters: instructions, notes, correspondence, diagrams, 1951-1954 (Box 8:, Folder 131)
  - Reactors: Blueprints, 1942, 1945 (Box 8:, Folder 132)
  - Synchroscope: notes, correspondence, diagrams, drawings, instructions, blueprints, 1939, 1957 (Box 8:, Folder 133)
  - Watt-Hour Meters: instructions, drawings, notes, correspondence, invoices, 1946-1950 (Box 8:, Folder 134)
  - Type R / Types M & OB Meters: parts data, instructions, 1936-1945 (Box 8:, Folder 135)
  - Type R Meters - Correspondence: notes, correspondence, drawings, notes, 1944-1957 (Box 8:, Folder 136)
  - Frequency Meter: notes, catalogs, instructions, blueprints, correspondence, ca. 1941-1942 (Box 8:, Folder 137)
  - Leeds and Northrup Correspondence: correspondence, contracts, instructions, charts, notes, reports, 1947-1975 (Box 8:, Folder 138)
  - West Farms Ammeters: notes, drawings, instructions, specifications, blueprints, price quotations, ca. 1950-1981 (Box 8:, Folder 139)
  - Generator Armature Temperature Recording: blueprints, diagrams, notes, correspondence, 1945 (Box 8:, Folder 140)
  - Generator Field Temperature Recording: blueprints, correspondence, purchase orders, invoices, 1945 (Box 8:, Folder 141)
  - Catalogs - Leeds and Northrup; General / Manuals printed material, blueprints, correspondence, diagrams, instructions, catalogs, 1937-1950 (Box 8:, Folder 142)
  - Clocks and Recording Meters: specifications, instructions, diagrams, blueprints, 1950 (Box 8:, Folder 143)
  - AC Lighting Panel: notes, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 144)
  - Lincoln Thermal Converter: notes, printed material, 1939-1941 (Box 8:, Folder 145)
  - Printometer / Demand Meters: specifications, catalogs, correspondence, drawings, notes, 1936-1961 (Box 8:, Folder 146)
  - Demand Meters: catalogs, notes, diagrams, instructions, invoices, correspondence, invoices, 1936-1976 (Box 8:, Folder 147)
  - Contact Devices: instructions, notes, correspondence, drawings, ca. 1926-1950 (Box 8:, Folder 148)
  - 60 ∼ (?) (GE) Signal Regulator: notes, drawings, 1946-1950, 67 (Box 8:, Folder 149)
  - Smoke Detectors (Boilers 902, 903, 904): drawings, notes, punch cards, parts lists, instructions, catalogs, 1969-1972 (Box 8:, Folder 150)
  - Heathkit Clocks / Clocks parts lists, instructions, notes, 1973-1974 (Box 8:, Folder 151)
  - Test Instruments Industrial Analyzer: notes, drawings, instructions, diagrams, catalogs, 1935-1941 (Box 8:, Folder 152)
  - Test Instruments Instruments, Test and Portable: notes, invoices, correspondence, identification tags, blueprints, catalogs, instructions, printed materials, 1925-1945 (Box 8:, Folder 153)
  - Test Instruments High Voltage Indicator (Neon): instructions, 1941 (Box 8:, Folder 154)
  - Test Instruments Current / Potential Transformers: notes, instructions, blueprints, 1942-1945 (Box 8:, Folder 155)
  - Charts and Records: notes, disposal records, ca. 1950 (Box 8:, Folder 156)
  - Grounding: correspondence, 1949 (Box 8:, Folder 157)
  - Brush Data: notes, correspondence, catalogs, 1956, 1978 (Box 8:, Folder 158)
  - Fuses: notes, undated (Box 8:, Folder 159)
  - Lightning Arresters: notes, instructions, drawings, correspondence, 1941, 1951 (Box 8:, Folder 160)
  - Outdoor Underground Cable Runs: notes, blueprints, undated (Box 8:, Folder 161)
  - High Tension Knife Switches: notes, blueprints, correspondence, memos, 1948-1950 (Box 8:, Folder 162)
  - Rheostats: correspondence, blueprints, parts lists, 1952-1953 (Box 8:, Folder 163)
  - Shop Equipment Torches, Fire Pots, etc., Vacuum Cleaner: instructions, notes, specification, undated, 1948 (Box 8:, Folder 164)
  - Shop Equipment Rubber Gloves: correspondence, identification tags, notes, 1953-1974 (Box 8:, Folder 165)
  - Shop Equipment: specifications, diagrams, purchase orders, invoices, instructions, parts lists, 1947-1957, ca. 1975 (Box 8:, Folder 166)
  - Shop Equipment Liquid Storage Tanks: instructions, diagrams, 1975 (Box 8:, Folder 167)
  - Load Dispatchers Tower Equipment: blueprints, 1947 (Box 8:, Folder 168)
  - Lighting Station Lighting: diagrams, notes, drawings, blueprints, receipts, correspondence, instructions, 1942-1951 (Box 8:, Folder 169)
  - Lighting Switchboard Lighting: notes, invoices, blueprints, purchase orders, diagrams, data sheets, 1946-1956 (Box 8:, Folder 170)
  - Lighting Emergency Lighting: notes, drawings, undated (Box 8:, Folder 171)
  - Lighting Office Lighting, Washroom Lighting: correspondence, price quotations, catalogs, instructions, diagrams, blueprints, 1946-1947, 1954 (Box 8:, Folder 172)
  - Electric Motors, GE Switches, Contactors Relays: instructions, parts lists, 1926-1942 (Box 8:, Folder 173)
  - Electric Motors, Cutler-Hammer Parts: correspondence, catalogs, instructions, notes, parts lists, 1943-1967 (Box 8:, Folder 174)
  - Electric Motors Square D Company: instructions, 1945-1948 (Box 8:, Folder 175)
  - Spare Motors: notes, 1948 (Box 8:, Folder 176)
  - Files: clocks, switchboards, 1947, 1950 (Box 9:, Folder 177)
  - Files: lines east and west, feeder east and west, trolley east and west, var meter, 60∼ voltage, station / line voltmeters, Cos Cob load, West Farms load, system load, 25 ∼ frequency, 1946-1957 (Box 9:, Folder 178)
  - Files: generators, field temperature, armature temperature, GE demand, printometer, KWH meters, emergency lights and signals, control panel, indicating meters, 1945-1953 (Box 9:, Folder 179)
  - Files: 60∼ voltage regulators, relays - signals east and west, 1947-1966 (Box 9:, Folder 180)
  - Files: emergency signals / lighting, station alarm, KWH meters - Cos Cob, West Farms, 1942-1950 (Box 9:, Folder 181)
- Series IV: Boiler Office files, undated, 1921-1985
  - Ash and Soot - Conveyor Manual: instructions, ca. 1947 (Box 9:, Folder 182)
  - Ash and Soot - Blowers: instructions, diagrams, 1942-1944 (Box 9:, Folder 183)
  - Ash and Soot - Cottrells: correspondence, price quotations, inspection reports, invoices, var. dates (Box 9:, Folder 184)
  - Ash and Soot - United Conveyor Corporation: invoices, correspondence, purchase orders, drawings, diagrams, ca. 1945 (Box 9:, Folder 185)
  - Batteries: operating instructions, reports, 1952-1953 (Box 9:, Folder 186)
  - Boilers: correspondence, reports, notes, diagrams, sale flyers, proposals, 1925, 1977-1978, 1982 (Box 9:, Folder 187)
  - Boilers - Repairs: notes on costs, 1969-1977 (Box 9:, Folder 188)
  - Boilers - Performance Optimization Study: correspondence, report, 1976 (Box 9:, Folder 189)
  - Boiler Rehabilitation Project: contracts, proposals, correspondence, reports, price quotes, diagrams, 1976-1977 (Box 9:, Folder 190)
  - Budgets (MetroNorth): operating budget, capital budget, 1985 (Box 9:, Folder 191)
  - Circuit Breakers: manuals, instructions, catalogs, parts data, 1925-1950 (Box 9:, Folder 192)
  - Circuit Breakers - Type AB Automatic Circuit Breaker: specifications, reports, proposals, correspondence, notes, invoices, packing lists, receipts, price quotes, drawings, 1925-1957 (Box 9:, Folder 193)
  - Conduit Numbering: list of conduits, undated (Box 9:, Folder 194)
  - Correspondence - Responsibility for Maintenance and Numbering: correspondence, 1924-1928 (Box 9:, Folder 195)
  - Correspondence - Plant Condition and Oversight: correspondence, 1924-1928 (Box 9:, Folder 196)
  - Devon - Emergency / Excess Power: correspondence to Ernest Green of Connecticut Light and Power, 1954-1961 (Box 9:, Folder 197)
  - Devon - Equipment, Inventories, Requisitions: correspondence, notes, reports, 1946-1958 (Box 9:, Folder 198)
  - Devon testing reports, repair records, notes (Box 9:, Folder 199)
  - Devon - Plans blueprints, diagrams, correspondence, drawings, 1927-1948 (Box 9:, Folder 200)
  - Devon - Weekly Reports testing reports, notes, ca. 1963-1964 (Box 9:, Folder 201)
  - East New York - Files notes, reports, drawings, blueprints, correspondence, testing reports, repair records, 1927-1968 (Box 9:, Folder 202)
  - Electrical: log sheets, tests, correspondence, testing procedures, drawings, undated (Box 10:, Folder 203)
  - Electrical High Tension Cable: meeting excerpts, correspondence, specifications, 1924-1925 (Box 10:, Folder 204)
  - Electrical Fittings and Parts correspondence, price changes, discount sheet, electrical wholesale catalog, test procedures, interim information, brochures, operating and service manual, 1948-1964 (Box 10:, Folder 205)
  - Electrical Controller Parts: Brownell, Cutler-Hammer merchandiser, renewal guide, price lists, correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 10:, Folder 206)
  - Electrical Switches correspondence, brochures, catalogs, 1956 (Box 10:, Folder 207)
  - Environmental Weather Charts, 1967 May (Box 10:, Folder 208)
  - Environmental Visible Emissions Monitoring brochure, instructions, blueprint, parts catalog, correspondence quotation, advertisement (Box 10:, Folder 209)
  - Environmental Air Pollution Petition, correspondence, court report, order to Cos Cob Plant, explanatory decision memorandum, 1975 (Box 10:, Folder 210)
  - Environmental Air Pollution Sample analysis, correspondence, final order of EPA, errata advice, notification letter, proposed regulations registration certificate, petitioner's brief, service receipt, 1976 January - June (Box 10:, Folder 211)
  - Environmental Air Pollution Correspondence, coal analysis, complaint, addendum, plaintiffs' notice, news clipping, order on plaintiffs' motion lab report, field report, inspection report, proposal, news clippings, 1976 June - December (Box 10:, Folder 212)
  - Environmental Air Pollution coal analysis reports, petition, service bill, strip charts, transcript of statements, 1977-1978 (Box 10:, Folder 213)
  - Floating Power Plants correspondence, 1976 (Box 10:, Folder 214)
  - Frequency Converter Manual, 1984 (Box 10:, Folder 215)
  - Fuel Conversion Correspondence, design consideration brochure, 1976 (Box 10:, Folder 216)
  - Inventory Procedures Conrail Instructions for physical inventory, 1979 (Box 10:, Folder 217)
  - Metro North Operating Procedures, 1985 (Box 10:, Folder 218)
  - Metro North Winterization Report on winterization preparations, equipment upgrade survey, 1980 (Box 10:, Folder 219)
  - Office Furnishing Invoice, correspondence, advertisement, 1948 (Box 10:, Folder 220)
  - Operations Handbook, 1950-1975 (Box 10:, Folder 221)
  - Personnel Memoranda of agreements, mediation agreement, provisions of acts, correspondence, supervisory development program, job descriptions, news clippings, survey, electrical information, laws of New York, 1954-1977 (Box 10:, Folder 222)
  - Personnel Vacations Attendance records, 1952-1956 (Box 10:, Folder 223)
  - Personnel International Brotherhood of electrical workers Correspondence, training evaluation review forms, 1951-1977 (Box 10:, Folder 224)
  - Personnel International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers Correspondence, complaints, claims receipts, time card, 1956-1975 (Box 10:, Folder 225)
  - Personnel Observation summaries Safety rules observation summary, personal injury report accident prevention observation, 1975-1977 (Box 10:, Folder 226)
  - Personnel Conrail training manual “High voltage theory and techniques”, 1980 (Box 10:, Folder 227)
  - Personnel Applications and employments, 1921- (Box 11:, Folder 228)
  - Personnel NH Service record cards, to 1967 (Box 11:, Folder 229)
  - Personnel NH Conrail Amtrak service records, 1968- (Box 11:, Folder 230)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 11:, Folder 231)
    - • 1988-0024.ph1 - “Rear of Plant showing Electrostatic Cinder Eliminators, induced draft fans, ash conveyors and stacks. Brick stack shows boiler #904. Short stack servers boilers #902 and #903. Tall steel stack serves boilers #900 and #901.”
    - • 1988-0024.ph2 - “Southeast corner of plant showing south bunkercoal conveyor, feeder towers, and ash conveyor pipe.”
    - • 1988-0024.ph3 - “11,000 volt, 3 phase tie in lines to consolidated Edison Co., adjacent to the plant.”
    - • 1988-0024.ph4 - “Coal unlading station showing yard conveyers, bulldozer, and storage pile.”
    - • 1988-0024.ph5 - “Ash disposal area showing C.L.&P. transmission tower.”
    - • 1988-0024.ph6 - “Ash disposal area showing pipe discharge.”
    - • 1988-0024.ph7 - “Electrical control room showing generator, signal, and local service panels.”
    - • 1988-0024.ph8 - “Front of boilers #902, #903, and #904 showing control panels and coal hoppers.”
    - • 1988-0024.ph9 - “Boiler feed water pumps”
    - • 1988-0024.ph10 - “One of the two coal pulverizer mills for boiler #904.”
    - • 1988-0024.ph11 - “Ash hopper, boiler # 904, showing ash conveyor intakes.”
    - • 1988-0024.ph12 - “Signal power motor generator sets.”
    - • 1988-0024.ph13 - “Main turbine generator sets.”
    - • 1988-0024.ph14 - “7200 KVA auto-transformers, 11000-22000 volt.”
    - • 1988-0024.ph15 - “22000 volt switch gear - east switch house.”
    - • 1988-0024.ph16 - “440 volt metal-clad local service switch gear and bus structure.”
    - • 1988-0024.ph17 - “11000 volt switch gear - stat bus.”
    - • 1988-0024.ph18 - “Generator cooling air washer.”
    - • 1988-0024.ph19 - “Mianus pumping station and dam.”
    - • 1988-0024.ph20 - “Diesel engines and pumps at Mianus pumping station.”
    - • 1988-0024.ph21 - “Unidentified company executives.”
  - Plans, 1927, 1937 (Box 11:, Folder 232)
  - Various manufacturers, 1947
  - Blue prints
  - Plans, 1923-1928 (Box 11:, Folder 233)
  - 6-D blueprints by Gibbs & Hill Consulting Engineers, NY
  - 9000 KW Turbine No. 1, Turbine Room Floor Framing, 6D-291, 1923 February 1
  - Steel support for 9000 KW Turbine, generator #1, sheet #1, 6D-294, 1923 February 1
  - Control and Lighting Conduit Gallery Floor, 6D-591, undated
  - Typical cross-section looking east, 6D-595, 1926 February 9
  - Electrical Connections H.T. 220000V, bus structure for transformer switching, 6D-600, undated
  - Diff. Proj & Battery Floating SW, Board Wiring Diagram (rear view), 6D-1010, 1928 December 31
  - Plans, 1928 (Box 11:, Folder 234)
  - 6-S blueprints by Gibbs & Hill Consulting Engineers, NY Main Structure diagram, 6S-1001, 1928 December 31
  - Control Switch Board Wiring Diagram (rear view), 6S-1002, 1928 December 31
  - Exciter Switch Board Wiring Diagram (rear view), 6S-1003, 1928 December 31
  - Feeder Board, Wiring Diagram (rear view), 6S-1004, 1928 December 31
  - “MC” Temper & “Co” Relay Brd. Wiring Diagram (rear view), 6S-1005, 1928December 31
  - Recording Motor Board Wiring Diagram (rear view), 6S-1006, 1928 December 31
  - Bench Board Wiring Diagram (rear view), 6S-1007, 1928 December 31
  - Instrument Board, Wiring Diagram (rear view), 6S-1008, 1928 December 31
  - 60∼ Signal Board Wiring Diagram (rear view), 6S-1009, 1928 December 31
  - Plan, 1925 (Box 11:, Folder 235)
  - 6-X blueprints by Gibbs & Hill Consulting Engineers, NY Proposed arrangement of Cur. Trans. For Diff. Protection of New Generators no. 1, 2, 3, & 4, 6X-573, 1925 October 19
  - Plans, 1945-1952 (Box 11:, Folder 236)
  - 550E and 550 X blueprints
  - Plans, 1946-1952 (Box 11:, Folder 237)
  - NH blueprints
  - Plans, 1918-1924 (Box 11:, Folder 238)
  - Westinghouse (#3) blueprints
  - 12 in. Comb. Globe & Auto Throttle Valve (42-47-40), 1917
  - Stop Gov Trip Gear Assembly & Bill (42-44-32), 1917
  - Steam Turbine, Oil Pump Assembly & Bill (86236), 1918
  - K.V.A. Revolving Field A.C. Generator (42-55-99), 1918
  - Spindle Clearances (42-55-29), 1918
  - Steam Turbine, Oil Piping Assembly (62-01-95), 1920
  - Steam Turbine Oil Pipe Assembly (42-54-74), 1920
  - E.H.N.C. Steam Turbine Assembly (42-69-80), 1921
  - Steam Chest Assembly (42-57-45), 1922
  - Governor Assembly (42-02-62), undated
  - Plans, 1922-1926 (Box 11:, Folder 239)
  - Westinghouse (#4) blueprints
  - Frame 22 S.S. W.L. Condenser (5-16-00-36), 1923
  - Governor Linkage and Steam Piping Assembly & Bill (5-06-00-57), 1922
  - Outline of S.S. W.L. Condenser for NYNH&HRR Co. (4-16-04-84), 1922
  - Bed Plate Drilling for Foundation Bolts (4-06-23-04), 1924
  - Auto Stop Governor Assembly & Bill (4-06-04-98), 1923
  - Outline of Exhaust Connection for NYNH&HRR Co. (3-16-12-09), 1926
  - Outline of Exhaust Connection for NYNH&HRR Co. (3-16-02-74), 1922
  - 128 C. W. Steam Turbine Thrust Bearing Lock Assembly & Bill (3-06-02-38), 1922
  - Foundation Bolts for NYNH&HRR Co. (1-16-02-53), 1922
  - Plans, 1945-1948 (Box 11:, Folder 240)
  - Westinghouse plans blueprints
  - Low Voltage Metal Enclosed Switchgear (47-J-947), 1945
  - 440 Volt Control Board (19-A-7364), 1945
  - Main Relay Board 11KV Panels 3 to 6 Wiring Diagram (19-A-7357), 1945
  - Main Control Board (19-A-7355), 1947
  - Bkr. Control Schemes (19-A-7352), 1947
  - Circuits (19-A-7351), 1947
  - Nameplate Lettering Chart (14-B-6817), undated
  - Nameplate Lettering Chart (14-B-6956), undated
  - Nameplate Lettering Chart (14-B-6550), undated
  - Frame Mtd. Outline Assembly (13-B-8856), 1945
  - Supervisory Control Escutcheons - esc. Lettering chart (7-C-6757), 1948
  - Power Management General Correspondence, instructions, bulletin order, 1932-1973 (Box 12:, Folder 241)
  - Power management Grids, telephone diagram, 1932, 1940 (Box 12:, Folder 242)
  - Power Management Load shedding, 1958-1965 (Box 12:, Folder 243)
  - Power Management Losses, shutdowns Diagram, blueprint, operation test results and report, 3 phase power supply list, correspondence, procedure during 1961 strike, shutdown reports, 1949, 1962-1969 (Box 12:, Folder 244)
  - Power production Costs Data Electrical statements, annual reports, monthly expense reports, contract power costs, 1961-1966 (Box 12:, Folder 245)
  - Power management Final shutdown strategy (CCPS) Correspondence, planned budget costs, plans, ca. 1980 (Box 12:, Folder 246)
  - “Signals” power Information on sixty cycle signal system, testing plans, schematic diagrams, 1948 (Box 12:, Folder 247)
  - Sleet melting memorandum, sleet melting scheme, instructions, correspondence, demand metering and billing procedure, 1939-1950 (Box 12:, Folder 248)
  - Spec 550-02 Correspondence, invoices, receipts, specifications for current limiting reactors, 1945 (Box 12:, Folder 249)
  - Spec 550-03 Specifications for 440 volt switchgear, 1945 (Box 12:, Folder 250)
  - Spec 550-04 Specifications for relay switchboard and current transformers, 1945 (Box 12:, Folder 251)
  - Spec 550-05 Specifications for main control and instrument switchboard, 1945 (Box 12:, Folder 252)
  - Spec 550-06 Specifications foe varnished cambric insulated cable with shielding tape, neoprene sheath and flameproof braid for 12000 volt service, 1945 (Box 12:, Folder 253)
  - Spec 550-07 440 volt control, instrument and relay switchboard, 1945 (Box 12:, Folder 254)
  - Spec 550-08 150 KVA lighting transformers, 1945 (Box 12:, Folder 255)
  - Spec 550 Correspondence, drawing list, bus changes, 1945-1946 (Box 12:, Folder 256)
  - Spec 550 Meetings and related Memoranda, 1945-1947 (Box 12:, Folder 257)
  - Steam turbine Inspection proposal and report, 1976 (Box 12:, Folder 258)
  - Turbo Generators Correspondence, engineering and supervision of repairs report, invoices, BEI study of #3 turbo, inspection proposals, 1974-1981 (Box 12:, Folder 259)
  - Upgrade, Conrail Blueprints, plans, drawings, 1979 (Box 12:, Folder 260)
  - Voltage Regulators, 1923-1957 (Box 12:, Folder 261)
  - Water: filtering and softening Operating instructions, 1979 (Box 12:, Folder 262)
  - West Farms Data and Equipment Relay data, instructions for oil circuit breaker, diagrams, correspondence, 1936-1952 (Box 12:, Folder 263)
  - West Farms Letter File Correspondence, memoranda, diagrams, minutes, billing dates, tap changing schedule, data sheets, 1936-1975 (Box 12:, Folder 264)
  - West Farms Plans, Diagrams, blueprints, 1936-1953 (Box 12:, Folder 265)
  - Woodmont Miscellaneous Enclosed type capacitor equipment report, proposals, test charts, correspondence, drawings, voltage readings, 1945-1971 (Box 12:, Folder 266)
  - Woodmont Plans Blueprints, diagrams, 1945-1949 (Box 12:, Folder 267)
- Series V: Boiler Office log sheets and repair records, 1926-1986
  - Boiler Room log sheets, 1986 January 1 - 1986 May 31 (Box 13:, Folder 268)
  - Boiler Room log sheets, 1986 June 1 - 1986 October 3 (Box 13:, Folder 269)
  - Operations Coal received, 1942 February - 1942 July (Box 13:, Folder 270)
  - Operations Coal received, 1944 August -1945 April (Box 13:, Folder 271)
  - Operations Coal received, 1945 December - 1948 April (Box 13:, Folder 272)
  - Operations Daily Coal Sheets, 1961 December 30 - 1966 December 31 (Box 13:, Folder 273)
  - Operations Study - Dust from coal Storage facilities, 1980 (Box 13:, Folder 274)
  - Operations Finishing log, 1947 December 30 - 1948 August 27, 1952 August 14 - 1953 May 24 (Box 13:, Folder 275)
  - Operations Foreman's log, 1926 August 25 - 1926 December 18 (Box 13:, Folder 276)
  - Operations Foreman's log, 1928 April 10 - 1928 August 10 (Box 13:, Folder 277)
  - Operations Foreman's log, 1928 August 11 - 1928 December 13 (Box 13:, Folder 278)
  - Operations Foreman's log, 1933 May 4 - 1933 September 4 (Box 13:, Folder 279)
  - Operations Foreman's log, 1941 November 7 - 1942 March 11 (Box 13:, Folder 280)
  - Operations Foreman's log, 1945 December 7 - 1946 April 7 (Box 13:, Folder 290)
  - Operations Foreman's log, 1952 January 1 - 1952 August 31 (Box 13:, Folder 291)
  - Operations Foreman's log, 1971 October 4 - 1972 April 20 (Box 13:, Folder 292)